Subtitle Provide by dramacool.asia Translator [Admin.@YNG]
تم توفير الترجمة بواسطة مترجم dramacool.asia [Admin.@YNG]
[Between Love and Frost]
[بين الحب والصقيع]
[Episode 3]
[الحلقة 3]
Glad to meet you, Tongpei.
يسعدني أن ألتقي بك، تونغبي.
Likewise, Minghui.
وبالمثل، مينغوي.
Pei,
يحب،
Minghui
مينغهوي
came to our city to do grain business.
جاء إلى مدينتنا للقيام بتجارة الحبوب.
She'll be a great help to our army.
ستكون بمثابة مساعدة كبيرة لجيشنا.
You two should keep in touch.
ينبغي لكما أن تبقيا على اتصال.
Sure, Mr. Gu.
بالتأكيد، السيد جو.
Father,
أب،
let's go have dinner.
دعنا نذهب لتناول العشاء.
Minghui has been busy all day
لقد كان مينغ هوي مشغولاً طوال اليوم
and hasn't eaten yet.
ولم يأكل بعد
Okay.
تمام.
Let's go for dinner.
دعنا نذهب لتناول العشاء.
I'm not hungry.
أنا لست جائعا.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
Are you okay?
هل أنت بخير؟
Excuse me.
اعذرني.
Did you see
هل رأيت
anyone pass by
أي شخص يمر
just now?
الآن؟
Seize the chance.
اغتنم الفرصة.
Don't let me down.
لا تخذلني.
Right here?
هنا بالضبط؟
You really think highly of me.
أنت حقا تعتقد أنني ذو قيمة كبيرة بالنسبة لي.
Once it's done,
بمجرد الانتهاء من ذلك،
I'll make sure you leave safely.
سأتأكد من مغادرتك بأمان.
Minghui, you look pale.
مينغوي، أنت تبدو شاحبًا.
Did you not sleep well?
هل لم تنم جيدا؟
You don't look too well either.
أنت لا تبدو بحالة جيدة أيضًا.
Poor sleep?
قلة النوم؟
I'm in my own home.
أنا في منزلي.
How could I not sleep well?
كيف لم أستطع النوم جيدا؟
Tongpei,
تونجبي,
what's the story with your new girl?
ما هي قصة فتاتك الجديدة؟
She's bold.
إنها جريئة.
Just...
فقط...
a wild kitten.
قطة برية.
Enjoy.
يتمتع.
I need to go.
انا بحاجه للذهاب.
Get along well,
توافق بشكل جيد،
you two.
انتما الاثنان.
Tongpei,
تونجبي,
the drawer in my dressing table is broken.
الدرج الموجود في طاولة الزينة الخاصة بي مكسور.
I'm wondering
انا اتساءل
if you can help me fix it.
إذا كان بإمكانك مساعدتي في إصلاحه.
Sure.
بالتأكيد.
Thanks so much for your help.
شكرا جزيلا لمساعدتك.
Would you want
هل تريد؟
any reward?
أي مكافأة؟
It's nothing.
لا شئ.
There's no need.
ليست هناك حاجة.
Were you
هل كنت
peeking at me?
تتطلع إلي؟
You seem to have no sense of boundaries.
يبدو أنك لا تملك أي إحساس بالحدود.
Tongpei,
تونجبي,
we are family.
نحن عائلة.
And this is your reward?
وهذه مكافأتك؟
Are you okay?
هل أنت بخير؟
Who are you?
من أنت؟
Why do you want to kill me?
لماذا تريد قتلي؟
Do you ask every assassin
هل تسأل كل قاتل
their reason to kill you?
ما هو سبب قتلك؟
Lots of people want me dead.
الكثير من الناس يريدون موتي.
But you are the only one
ولكنك الوحيد
who dares to make a move here.
من يجرؤ على التحرك هنا.
Thanks for the compliment.
شكرا على الثناء.
Miss Chu,
الآنسة تشو،
is the Second Young Master with you?
هل الشاب الثاني معك؟
Minghui,
مينغهوي،
things in your room look fragile.
الأشياء في غرفتك تبدو هشة.
I'll keep an eye on them
سأبقي عينى عليهم
and help you fix them anytime.
ومساعدتك في إصلاحها في أي وقت.
Mr. Gu,
السيد جو،
Miss Chu Yan is here.
السيدة تشو يان هنا.
She's waiting in the parlor.
إنها تنتظر في الصالون.
Okay.
تمام.
Minghui, come along and meet her.
مينغ هوي، تعال والتقي بها.
Sure.
بالتأكيد.
Where's Chu Yan?
أين تشو يان؟
Pei,
يحب،
I missed you so much.
لقد افتقدتك كثيرا.
Pei.
يحب.
[Chu Yan]
[تشو يان]
Did you miss me?
هل إفتقدتني؟
This is...
هذا هو...
This is
هذا هو
Chu Minghui,,
تشو مينغوي،،
my sister-in-law.
أخت زوجي.
Oh, Miss Chu.
أوه، آنسة تشو.
You surely have good romantic luck.
من المؤكد أن لديك حظًا رومانسيًا جيدًا.
Hello, pretty.
مرحباً يا جميلة.
Pei,
يحب،
my father's away on business,
والدي مسافر في رحلة عمل
and no one's at home.
ولا أحد في المنزل.
I'll stay here
سأبقى هنا
tonight.
الليلة.
Suit yourself.
تناسب نفسك.
I brought you a present.
لقد جلبت لك هدية.
Lan, bring it over.
لان، أحضره.
Sorry, Miss Chu.
عذرا، آنسة تشو.
Sorry, Mr. Gu.
عذرا سيد جو.
It's okay.
لا بأس.
Leave it.
اتركه.
She's too clumsy.
إنها خرقاء للغاية.
I'll take care of her.
سأعتني بها.
You're truly kind-hearted,
أنت طيب القلب حقا،
though
رغم ذلك
there's no need
ليست هناك حاجة
to care so much about a maid.
الاهتمام بالخادمة كثيرا.
I need to ask you something.
أريد أن أسألك شيئا.
I'm busy. Another day.
أنا مشغول. يوم آخر.
Lan,
و،
does your hand still hurt?
هل لا تزال يدك تؤلمك؟
It's okay,
لا بأس،
Miss Chu.
السيدة تشو.
I can't believe you flirted with Pei
لا أستطيع أن أصدق أنك غازلت باي
right in front of me.
أمامي مباشرة.
How dare you?
كيف تجرؤ؟
That Chu Minghui
أن تشو مينغ هوي
also flirted with Pei right before my eyes.
لقد غازلت باي أيضًا أمام عيني.
Go and get something for me.
اذهب واحصل لي على شيء.
I want a snake.
أريد ثعبان.
Is she the one who saved me?
هل هي التي أنقذتني؟
Morning.
صباح.
I've made fresh soup.
لقد صنعت حساءً طازجًا.
Have a try.
جربه.
Snake soup needs to be drunk warm.
يجب شرب حساء الثعبان دافئًا.
It's nourishing.
إنه مغذي.
Yesterday,
أمس،
a good one gave me a gift.
لقد أعطاني شخص جيد هدية.
How did she know
كيف عرفت؟
since childhood, I've always been best
منذ الطفولة، كنت دائمًا الأفضل
at making snake soup?
في صنع حساء الثعبان؟
I always
انا دائما
repay favors.
رد الجميل.
I will find her
سوف أجدها
and thank her
وشكرها
with a good gift.
مع هدية جيدة.
Try it.
جربها.
I have things to do.
لدي أشياء للقيام بها.
I'll see you.
سوف أراك.
You're not having it?
أنت لا تقبل ذلك؟
Little girl.
فتاة صغيرة.
Have some snake soup. It's nourishing.
تناول حساء الثعبان، فهو مُغذّي.
Good timing.
توقيت جيد.
Snake soup. It's nourishing.
حساء الثعبان. إنه مغذي.
Your skills
مهاراتك
aren't those of a trader.
أليست هذه من نصيب التاجر؟
What's your background really?
ما هي خلفيتك الحقيقية؟
Curious?
فضولي؟
Well,
حسنًا،
find me at the dance hall today.
ستجدني في قاعة الرقص اليوم.
Catch me in good spirits and I'll talk.
أمسكني وأنا في حالة معنوية جيدة وسأتحدث.
Sure.
بالتأكيد.
[Palace of Joy]
[قصر الفرح]
Minghui, it's loud here.
مينغ هوي، الصوت مرتفع هنا.
Not the place
ليس المكان
for sincere talk.
للحديث الصادق.
I'm sending you on your way.
سأرسلك في طريقك.
A bit of bustle is only fitting.
قليل من الصخب هو أمر مناسب.
There's a time and place to kill.
هناك وقت ومكان للقتل.
Don't hurt the innocent.
لا تؤذي الأبرياء.
Rest assured,
اطمئن، لا تشغل بالك،
they are all my people.
إنهم كلهم ​​شعبي.
Apologies.
اعتذارات.
Do you have any last words?
هل لديك أي كلمات أخيرة؟
I don't think I'm ready
لا أعتقد أنني مستعد
to die young just yet.
أن تموت شابا حتى الآن.
In ten minutes,
في عشر دقائق،
cut all the power here.
قطع كل الطاقة هنا.
Yes, sir.
نعم سيدي.
Don't fire and hit our own.
لا تطلق النار وتصيبنا.
Keep quiet.
ابقى هادئا.
Come with me.
تعال معي.
No tricks.
لا حيل.
I'll only ask once.
سأسأل مرة واحدة فقط.
Answer me properly.
أجبني بالشكل الصحيح.
Did you use to live
هل كنت تعيش من قبل؟
on the old street in the north?
في الشارع القديم في الشمال؟
How do you know?
كيف علمت بذلك؟
Leave the Mansion.
أترك القصر.
What if...
ماذا إذا...
I refuse?
انا ارفض؟
♪Love is an abyss one cannot escape♪
"الحب هو الهاوية التي لا يمكن الهروب منها"
♪The more I doubt, the more I fear♪
كلما زاد شكي زاد خوفي
♪Sparks of hatred ignite within the heart♪
???شرارات الكراهية تشتعل في القلب؟؟؟
♪The more I struggle, the hoarser my voice becomes♪
كلما زاد جهدي، أصبح صوتي أكثر خشونة؟؟؟
♪I guard myself over and over again♪
???أحمي نفسي مرارا وتكرارا؟؟؟
♪I hesitate in every word and every moment♪
???أتردد في كل كلمة وفي كل لحظة؟؟؟
♪I feign, struggle♪
???أنا أتظاهر، أكافح؟؟؟
♪Flee, and break♪
???الفرار والانكسار؟؟؟
♪The endless shackle of darkness♪
???قيود الظلام التي لا نهاية لها؟؟؟
♪Let the hatred go♪
???دع الكراهية تذهب؟؟؟
♪Don't dwell♪
???لا تتوقف؟؟؟
♪Only when flowers wither will scars form♪
"فقط عندما تذبل الزهور تتكون الندوب"
♪Let love and hate scatter with the wind♪
???دع الحب والكراهية يتناثران مع الريح؟؟؟
♪Let myself be free♪
???اسمح لنفسي أن أكون حرا؟؟؟